Guide to the James Cecil Nelson Papers 1934-1975
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
James Cecil Nelson Papers
1934-1975
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections Pullman, WA 99164-5610 USA (509) 335-6691 http://www.wsulibs.wsu.edu/masc/ mascref@wsu.edu
Cage 369
Nelson, James Cecil
35 containers. 24.5 linear feet of shelf space. 8950 items.
Correspondence, reports, government documents, statistics, unpublished papers, reprints, clippings, memoranda, student papers, and other materials related to teaching, researching, writing, and consulting about transportation economics, particularly railroads and the Interstate Commerce Commission.
Professor Emeritus James Cecil Nelson, internationally known transportation economist, was born in Bickleton, Washington, on October 5, 1908. Nelson received his B.A. from the University of Washington in 1930, his M.A. from Ohio State University in 1931, and his Ph.D. from the University of Virginia in 1934. Nelson was a Dupont fellow, 1932-1934, and also a research fellow at the Brookings Institution from 1933 to 1934. After receiving his doctorate, Nelson served on the faculties of several universities and also worked for more than a year with the Washington Department of Public Service. In 1938 Nelson joined the Bureau of Agricultural Economics, U.S. Department of Agriculture, as a senior transportation economist. In 1941 he became the principal transportation economist with the National Resources Planning Board.
During the Second World War, Nelson worked with a number of Federal agencies. He served first as assistant director in charge of regulatory policy studies, Division of Economic Studies, Board of Investigation and Research (1941-1944), and later as assistant director, Division of Review and Special Studies, Office of Defense Transportation (1944-1945). Before returning to academic life in 1947, he served as chief of the Transportation Division, Office of Domestic Commerce, U.S. Department of Commerce (1945-1947).
In 1947 Nelson joined the faculty of Washington State University as professor of economics and transportation in the Department of Economics, a position he held until his retirement in September 1974. In addition to his teaching, research, and writing at WSU, Nelson served as a consultant for the Washington State Legislature's Joint Fact-Finding Committee on Highways, Streets, and Bridges, as well as the Legislative Research Committee of the North Dakota Legislature (1948-1952). He also served as a consultant for, among others: the Royal Commission on Transportation, Alberta, Canada (1960); the Federation of Nigeria (1960-1961); the Royal Government of Afganistan (1963); Pembina Pipe Line Limited, Calgary, Alberta (1961, 1962); A.T.and S.F.; Railway (1961-1968); American Automobile Manufacturers Association (1966); and the Pacific Island Tariff Bureau (1969). In 1956-1957, Nelson was a senior staff member at the Brookings Institution. He also served as visiting professor at the University of Wisconsin (1964), University of British Columbia (fall, 1975), and Monash University, Melbourne, Australia (1975). Nelson's research has resulted in numerous articles in professional journals and a number of books, among which are: Railroad Transportation and National Policy (1959), Transportation Problems and Policies in the Trans-Missouri West (1967), The Future of American Transportation (1971), Perspectives on Regional Transportation Planning (1973), Perspectives on Federal Transportation Policy (1975), and Railway Pricing under Commercial Freedom: The Canadian Experience (1977).
The papers of James Cecil Nelson are arranged in four series: Research Files, 1934-1947; Correspondence and Student Placement Files, 1938-1975; Instructional Material and Related Research Files, 1932-1974; and Professional Activities, 1947-1975. The first series, Research Files, 1934-1947, is divided into two subseries: Academic and State Appointments, 1934-1938; and the Federal Service, 1938-1947. Included in the Academic and State Appointments subseries are a transportation bibliography, employment correspondence for 1938, and a field book compiled by Nelson when he worked for the Washington Department of Public Services in 1936. The second series, Federal Service, 1938-1947 is arranged chronologically by the positions Nelson held with the federal government, that is, with the Bureau of Agricultural Economics, 1938-1941, the Board of Investigation and Research, 1941-1944, and the Department of Commerce, 1944-1947. This material is arranged alphabetically within each of these groups. Included in this subseries are some correspondence, reports, research materials, publications, and memoranda.
In the second series, Correspondence and Student Placement Files, 1938-1975, is divided into two subseries: Correspondence, 1938-1967, and student Placement Files, 1952-1975. The correspondence is arranged alphabetically by subject and includes both incoming and outgoing letters to individuals, professional and business organizations, federal agencies, state legislative committees, and publishers. The student placement files are arranged alphabetically by the name of the firm or corporation involved, such as Great Northern, New York Central, and Shell Oil. Included in this subseries are letters from Nelson to personnel officers and other executives on behalf of various students, as well as. information on the various companies and their policies and opportunities.
The third series, Transport Economics Courses and Research Files, 1932-1974 is arranged by course number. The material collected for use and research in the various courses is arranged alphabetically by subject within each particular course. The material for the ten different courses includes correspondence, reports, memoranda, published documents (federal, state and private), newspaper and magazine clippings, trade journals, court and Interstate Commerce Commission decisions, statistical surveys and professional reference papers, analysis of almost every aspect of transportation, research notes, projects, addresses, studies and student papers. One of Dr. Nelson's primary interests was rail transportation; consequently, the course entitled Land Transportation Agencies (Economics 464) which deals at length with rail transportation, comprises the majority of the material in this series.
The fourth series, Professional Activities, 1947-1975, is composed of two subseries: Consultation and Testimony, 1951-1967; and Publications, 1947-1975. The first subseries, Consultation and Testimony, is arranged alphabetically by subject and consists of material pertaining to Dr. Nelson's consulting work for private business, professional organizations, foreign countries, Canadian provinces, and states, as well as his testimony before various federal committees and commissions. This subseries includes Nelson's testimony before the Senate Select Committee on Small Businesses (1955) and the Interstate Commerce Commission (1970), consulting work for the Royal (Canadian) Commission on Transportation and the Province of Alberta, as well as documents, reports, legal decisions, correspondence, notes, publications, railroad rate information, and notes pertaining to both consultation and cases in which Dr. Nelson was interested. The second subseries, Publications, 1947-1975, pertains to Dr. Nelson's writing and publishing. The conferences are listed alphabetically by the sponsoring organization. The publications or papers which Nelson reviewed are listed alphabetically by author or generating body. Conference papers presented by Dr. Nelson are arranged alphabetically by the title of the paper, except under the folder heading "Conference Papers presented by Nelson, 1941-1973" in which the papers are arranged chronologically. Accompanying some of the conference papers are various research materials. Nelson's publications and accompanying research papers are arranged alphabetically by the title of the publication. With the majority of Dr. Nelson's publications are also correspondence (either with publisher, critics, or research sources), manuscripts, galley proofs, and other research material.
This collection is open for research use.
The James Cecil Nelson papers were donated br Dr. Nelson to the Washington State University Libraries in January 1977 (UA 77-2).
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Nelson, James C., 1908- --Archives
United States. Interstate Commerce Commission
Railroads -- United States--Finance; Transportation --United States--Finance; Economics -- Study and teaching (Higher)--Washington (State)--Pullman
Transportation; Washington (State)
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.
- Series 1: Research Files, 1934-1947
  - Academic and State Appointments, 1934-1938
    - Bibliography, Transport Topices, 1934-1937; 14 items. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Employment Correspondence, 1938; 16 items. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Field Book, Washington Department of Public Service, 1936; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Federal Service, 1938-1947
    - Bureau of Agricultural Economics, 1938-1941
      - Freight Rates Behavior and Structure, ms. by John D. Summner, 1939; 13 items. (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Interterritorial Rate Problem, 1939; 16 items. (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Morrison, Hunter. Motor Carrier research and ms., 1940-1941; 54 items. (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
      - Motor Freight Carrier Cases, 1938-1940; 60 items. (Box 1, Folder 8-13)
      - Motor Freight Rate Proceedings of I.C.Q., undated; 1 item. (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Motor Rate Study, 1940; 10 items. (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Rate Policy, 1939-1940; 28 items. (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Transportation Research Suggestions, 1939-1940; 23 items. (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Trucking Industry, Economic Characteristics, 1940; 46 items. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Board of Investigation and Research, 1941-1944
      - Freight Rates: Outline, 1942-1943; 30 items. (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Interstate Rate Problem Material, 40 items. (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Railroad Financing Report, 1941; 1 item. (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Rate Policy, 1941-1943; 45 items. (Box 2, Folder 22-24)
      - Research Program, 1942-1943; 10 items. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - United States Department of Commerce, 1945-1947
      - Air Cargo Service Survey, Field Office Returns, February-March 1947; 3 items. (Box 2, Folder 26-28)
      - Air Transportation Research, 1946-1947; 45 items. (Box 2, Folder 29-30)
      - Mountain-Pacific Traffic Flows, 1946-1947; 220 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Publications, Transportation Division, 1946-1947; 65 items. (Box 2, Folder 32-33)
      - Rate and Traffic Pattern Analysis, 1945-1946; 95 items. (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - Transportation Economics Research Notebook, 1946-1947; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Western United States Industrial Development, 1945-1947; 60 items. (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Series 2: Correspondence and Student Placement Files, 1938-1975
  - Correspondence
    - American Association of University Professors, 1952-1955; 95 items. (Box 3, Folder 37-38)
    - American Council on Education, Highway Research Board, 1951-1952; 6 items. (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - American Economic Association, 1948-1950; 1954-1956; 80 items. (Box 3, Folder 40-42)
    - Carll, Richard, 1954-1955; 15 items. (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Clay Committee Report, 1956; 30 items. (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Commerce, U.S. Department, 1948-1957; 40 items. (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Dodge, William, 1951-1955; 70 items. (Box 3, Folder 46-47)
    - Econometric Society, 1955; 20 items. (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Highway Research Board: Current Committee on Highway Taxation and Finance, 1950-1957; 70 items. (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Mater, Dan. H., 1947-1948; 25 items. (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Pacific Logging Congress, 1950; 5 items. (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Pacific Northwest Trade Association, 1955; 40 items. (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Publishers, 1938-1949; 60 items. (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Sillcox, L. K. Visit to WSU for American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1951-1954; 20 items. (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Spokane Chamber of Commerce, 1956; 8 items. (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Transportation, Department of. Office of Economics, Research Program, 1967; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Washington. Legislature, Joint Fact-Finding Committee on Highways, Streets, and Bridges, 1949-1951; 70 items. (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Washington State University. Committees and Correspondence, 1951-1953; 10 items. (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Western Economic Association, 1949-1955; 65 items. (Box 3, Folder 59-60)
  - Student Placement
    - Placement Files, 1952-1975; 235 items. (Box 4, Folder 61-67)
- Series 3: Transport Economics Courses and Research Files, 1932-1974
  - Econ. 165: Current Transportation Problems:
    - Agricultural Commodities Rates, publications, 1934-1952; 6 items. (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Canned Goods Rates, Northwest Canners Association, 1948-1952; 20 items. (Box 4, Folder 69-70)
    - Lumber Rate Structure, Pacific Northwest, 1952; 13 items. (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Student Reports, Current Transportation Problems, 1952; 10 items. (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Western States Council, 1948-1952; 45 items. (Box 4, Folder 73-74)
  - Econ. 167: Air and Water Transport:
    - Student Paper: The Brief History of Through Routes and Joint Rates for Grain and Petroleum on the Columbia River, Erle O. Anderson, 1952; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Econ 184: Advanced Economic Theory:
    - Student Papers, 1948; 1952; 6 items. (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Econ 197: Problems in Economics:
    - Student Papers, Economics of Navigation Subsidy in the Mid-Columbia River, James B. Willis, 1952; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Econ. 364: Transport Economics:
    - Railroad Problems and Progress, 1948-1969; 40 items. (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Student Papers, Inland Waterway Transport, 1959; 1968; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Transport Economics Readings, 1962-1971; 10 items. (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Econ. 463: Current Transportation Problems:
    - Rate Structure, Rates, Traffic Flow, 1947-1962; 20 items. (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Econ. 464: Land Transportation Agencies:
    - Congressional Documents on Transportation, 1932-1963; 27 items. (Box 5, Folder 82-85)
    - Economic and Business Research, Bureau of. Distribution and Service Industries Washington Transportation, 1955-1964; 25 items. (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Federal Aid Highway Act of 1956, 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Foreign Transport Files:
      - Bolivia and South America: Role of Transport in Development, 1963-1965; 20 items. (Box 5, Folder 88)
      - Nigerian Transport, 1961-1969; 25 items. (Box 5, Folder 89)
      - Pakistan Transport, 1959-1963; 6 items. (Box 5, Folder 90)
      - Transport in Foreign Countries, 1958-1966; 30 items. (Box 5, Folder 91)
      - Transport in Less Developed Countries, 1958-1962; 45 items. (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Highway Research Board: Committee on Highway Taxation and Finance, 1960-1965; 12 items. (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - How Rails Can Meet Competition, 1961; 1963; 60 items. (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Inland Freight Traffic Service, Transportation Digest, 1967-1974; 60 items. (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Intermodal Transport:
      - Clipping File, 1967-1969; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 96)
      - Columbia River Barge Transport; Rates and Traffic, 1933-1965; 20 items. (Box 6, Folder 97)
      - Columbia River Navigation Improvement, 1958-1959; 20 items. (Box 6, Folder 98)
      - Containerization, 1966-1971; 110 (Box 6, Folder 99-100)
      - Fair Sharing ICC Decisions - Rail Roads, 1957-1965; 60 items. (Box 6, Folder 101)
      - Federal Maritime Commission Documents, 1970-1974; 20 items. (Box 6, Folder 102)
      - ICC Documents, 1970; 15 items. (Box 6, Folder 103-104)
      - Overmyer, Daniel. Intermodal Transport Coordination, 1961-1969; 50 items. (Box 6, Folder 105)
      - Pipeline Transport, 1946-1952; 20 items. (Box 6, Folder 106)
      - Sea-Land, Seatrain Rate Case Decisions, 1961-1963; 8 items. (Box 6, Folder 107)
      - Sea-Land, Seatrain Rate Case Supreme Court Decisions, 1960-1967; 15 items. (Box 6, Folder 108)
      - Shipping week, 1969; 5 items. (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Kaiser Aluminum and Chemical Corp., 1960-1965; 25 items. (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Land Transportation Agencies, Notes, 1958-1962; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Mater Testimony and ICC Report in Ex Parte No. 166, 1947-1951; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - McGillivary, Robert. Transport Economics Papers, 1969-1974; 9 items. (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Motor Transportation:
      - Highway Finance - Date, 1948-1955; 30 items. (Box 7, Folder 114)
      - Highway Studies, General, 1948-1962; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 115)
      - Highway System, U.S., 1946-1955; 40 items. (Box 7, Folder 116)
      - Highway Transport Economics, 1947-1954; 15 items. (Box 7, Folder 117)
      - Motor Freight Rates Studies and Investigations, Washington, 1948-1953; 5 items. (Box 7, Folder 118)
      - Motor Rate Increase Cases, General, 1947-1966; 25 items. (Box 7, Folder 119)
      - Pacific Northwest Trucking Investigation, 1947-1951; 4 items. (Box 7, Folder 120)
      - Public Roads, Bureau of. Highway Capacity Studies, 1949-1971; 10 items. (Box 7, Folder 121)
      - Trucking Industry, 1954-1965; 10 items. (Box 7, Folder 122)
      - Trucking Rate Decisions, WPSC and ICC, 1949-1954; 55 items. (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - National Transportation Act of 1969 and Surface Transport Act of 1972, 1969-1972; 15 items. (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Pacific Northwest, developments, 1949-1966; 10 items. (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Pacific Northwest Transportation Economics Publications, 1926-1965; 20 items. (Box 8, Folder 126-127)
    - Rail Transportation:
      - Commuter Railroads, 1958-1972; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 128)
      - Finance and Regulations Publications, 1934-1963; 8 items. (Box 8, Folder 129)
      - Freight Car Shortages Conference, 1971; 10 items. (Box 8, Folder 130)
      - Freight Rate Problems, Pacific Northwest:
        - Bull, Alex, M. Analysis for Mr. J. J. Frawley of Reports of the Interstate Commerce Commission Which Resulted in the Present Adjustment of Transcontinental Rates to Spokane, Washington, 1947; 1 (Box 8, Folder 131)
        - Burns, Bartlett. Economic Study - Mountain-Pacific Territory: re. Docket No. 28300, undated; 1 (Box 8, Folder 132)
        - Class Rate Investigations: ICC Notices and Reports, 1948-1957; 55 (Box 8, Folder 133)
        - Class Rate Problem of Pacific Northwest, 1947-1948; 10 (Box 8, Folder 134)
        - Class Rates, Mountain Pacific Case, 1945-1955; 15 (Box 8, Folder 135-136)
        - Davey, V. H., Spokesman Review Data, 1958-1960; 20 (Box 8, Folder 137)
        - Fourth Section Material, 1911-1961; 105 (Box 9, Folder 138-139)
        - Grain Transport Related Studies, 1951-1972; 4 (Box 9, Folder 140)
        - Intercontinental Rate Traffic and Rail Rate, Western Traffic Association Research Committee, 1959-1960; 10 (Box 9, Folder 141)
        - Milwaukee Road Grain Rates, Rosalia to Seattle, 1968; 55 (Box 9, Folder 142)
        - Northern Pacific Multiple Car Grain Rates, 1966-1968; 35 (Box 9, Folder 143-144)
        - Rate Bureaus: Department of Justice, 1942-1946; 20 (Box 9, Folder 145)
        - Rate Problems: Pacific Northwest, 1947-1955; 50 (Box 9, Folder 146)
        - Rate Research: Class Rates in Pacific Northwest - Dan Mater and WSU, 1948-1949; 15 (Box 9, Folder 147)
        - Tolan, Fred. Freight Traffic Consultant on Grain Hauling Rates, 1965-1967; 15 (Box 9, Folder 148)
      - Full Crew Laws Investigation, 1960; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 149)
      - High Speed Ground Transport, N.E. Corridor, 1960-1967; 60 items. (Box 9, Folder 150)
      - Interstate Commerce Commission Documents:
        - Discontinuance of Service, 1966; 1970; 6 (Box 9, Folder 151)
        - Increased Freight Rates, 1968-1970-1971; 4 (Box 9, Folder 152)
        - Increased Rail Passenger Fates, 1960; 5 (Box 9, Folder 153)
        - Ingot Molds Case: Competition between Railroads and Water Carriers, 1966; 4 (Box 10, Folder 154)
        - Mountain Pacific Class Rates, 1952; 2 (Box 10, Folder 155)
        - Per Diem, 1965; 2 (Box 10, Folder 156)
        - Rail Costs and Rate Studies, 1954-1961; 3 (Box 10, Folder 157)
        - Rail Costs Finding Procedures, 1948-1967; 12 (Box 10, Folder 158)
        - Rail Traffic Compared with Production, 1937-1952; 6 (Box 10, Folder 159)
        - Southeastern Association of Railroad and Utilities Commissioners vs. A.T. and S.F., 1959-1962; 2 (Box 10, Folder 160)
      - Northern Pacific Railway Discovery Trip, 1969; 30 items. (Box 10, Folder 161)
      - Passenger Deficit Problem, 1951-1964; 11 items. (Box 10, Folder 162)
      - Passenger Problems, 1968-1971; 85 items. (Box 10, Folder 163)
      - Passenger Trains, 1966-1972; 100 (Box 11, Folder 164)
      - Penn Central Reorganization, 1973; 6 items. (Box 11, Folder 165)
      - Piggyback Transport:
        - Addresses and Reports, 1958-1966; 70 (Box 11, Folder 166)
        - Carrier Facilities, Methods, Innovations, 1961-1963; 20 (Box 11, Folder 167)
        - Forgash, Morris, 1958-1962; 15 (Box 11, Folder 168)
        - ICC and Other Documents, 1961-1964; 30 (Box 11, Folder 169-170)
        - Lundy, Robert F. Ph.D. Project, 1963; 8 (Box 11, Folder 171)
        - Regulatory Cases and Issues, 1960-1972; 35 (Box 11, Folder 172)
        - Studies, 1959-1964; 20 (Box 11, Folder 173)
        - User Reaction, 1960-1963; 50 (Box 11, Folder 174)
      - Rail Line Solutions, 1969-1972; 35 items. (Box 11, Folder 175)
      - Rail Problems and Potentials, 1958-1970; 65 items. (Box 11, Folder 176)
      - Railpax Clipping File, 1971; 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 177)
      - Railroad Management, Pacific Northwest, 1970-1973; 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 178)
      - Railroad: Operation of Trucks, Pipelines, etc., 1954-1957; 30 items. (Box 11, Folder 179)
      - Railway Labor: Rules, Issues, Articles, 1949-1962; 25 items. (Box 11, Folder 180)
      - Railway Express Agency, 1954-1965; 40 items. (Box 12, Folder 181-182)
      - Rand Paper Clippings, 1970-1971; 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 183)
      - Rates and Pricing: Dr. Ford Edwards, 1950-1955; 7 items. (Box 12, Folder 184)
      - Rate Topics:
        - Agreed Rates: NYC Rug Case and Others, 1959-1960; 15 (Box 12, Folder 185)
        - Canned Goods Rates Between Pacific Coast and East, 1954-1965; 20 (Box 12, Folder 186)
        - Cargill Case, 1966-1967; 5 (Box 12, Folder 187)
        - Competitive Rate Cases, 1957-1961; 20 (Box 12, Folder 188)
        - Competitive Rates and Decisions, 1959-1960; 1 (Box 12, Folder 189)
        - Impact of Competition on Railroads, Transcontinental Cases, 1947-1961; 50 (Box 12, Folder 190)
        - Interterritorial Freight Rates, 1929-1947; 30 (Box 12, Folder 191)
        - Quantity Rate Discount and Incentive Rate Cases, 1960-1970; 50 (Box 12, Folder 192)
        - Rail Rate Cases, 1950-1964; 40 (Box 13, Folder 193)
        - Rail Revenue Distribution, Contribution by,Commodity Groups, 1941-1965; 15 (Box 13, Folder 194)
        - Rail Traffic Flow and Rates, Publications, 1951-1960; 15 (Box 13, Folder 195)
        - Rail Level Cases, 1944-1962; 15 (Box 13, Folder 196)
        - Whitten, Herbert O. Testimony in Paint Case, 1955-1959; 15 (Box 13, Folder 197)
      - St. Lawrence Seaway and Related Projects, 1953-1959; 35 items. (Box 13, Folder 198)
      - Technology, 1958-1966; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 199)
      - Transport Efficiency and Productivity, 1954; 1970-1972; 12 items. (Box 13, Folder 200)